<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>I&#x27;m Win!</title>
    <link href="https://imwin.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://imwin.org" />
    <updated>2023-07-25T07:52:14+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Winrich</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://imwin.org</id>

    <entry>
        <title>如果正确操作期货</title>
        <author>
            <name>Winrich</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://imwin.org/trades.html"/>
        <id>https://imwin.org/trades.html</id>
            <category term="Trades"/>

        <updated>2023-07-25T07:52:14+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    trades
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>trades</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Developing My Own Trading Methodology to Rejoin Futures Market</title>
        <author>
            <name>Winrich</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://imwin.org/developing-my-own-trading-methodology-to-rejoin-futures-market.html"/>
        <id>https://imwin.org/developing-my-own-trading-methodology-to-rejoin-futures-market.html</id>
            <category term="Blog"/>

        <updated>2023-07-25T04:32:38+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I’m Winrich, 40 years old. I entered the futures market in 2008 but unfortunately encountered the subprime mortgage crisis. I then switched to run a clothing business for years. When the COVID-19 pandemic erupted in 2020, clothing orders dropped sharply, so I decided to return&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I’m Winrich, 40 years old. I entered the futures market in 2008 but unfortunately encountered the subprime mortgage crisis. I then switched to run a clothing business for years. When the COVID-19 pandemic erupted in 2020, clothing orders dropped sharply, so I decided to return to the familiar futures market and trade using my self-developed trading methodology.</p>
<h2 id="developing-cycle-trading-methodology">Developing Cycle Trading Methodology</h2>
<p>From operating the clothing business, I learned risk management and cost control skills. I applied these ideas to trading and devised the <strong>cycle trading methodology</strong>.</p>
<p>Its <strong>core concepts</strong> are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Analyze historical price trends to determine market cycles</li>
<li>Identify cycle multiple patterns</li>
<li>Take corresponding trading strategies based on cycle analysis</li>
</ul>
<p>This trading methodology assisted me to rejoin futures trading and achieve steady profits.</p>
<h2 id="success-stories">Success Stories</h2>
<p>Let me provide two examples to demonstrate applying the cycle trading methodology:</p>
<h3 id="case-one-glass-futures-contract">Case One: Glass Futures Contract</h3>
<p>In spring 2020, with the benefits of COVID-19 and construction peak season, the glass 2009 contract price surged from CNY1820/ton to a historic high of CNY2450/ton. </p>
<p>Based on cycle analysis, I went long around CNY2100 with about 70 tons. I timely locked profits when price hit CNY2450. By closing out positions at CNY2300 during the pullback, I gained about CNY350,000 in profits, around 1.75 times of the investment.</p>
<h3 id="case-two-soda-ash-futures-contract">Case Two: Soda Ash Futures Contract</h3>
<p>In the first half of 2022, soda ash futures plunged from CNY6950/ton to a historic low of CNY2860/ton. I judged there was more room to fall and went short around CNY5500 with about 45 tons.</p>
<p>After hitting the bottom at CNY2860, I covered positions at CNY3300 and obtained around CNY1.05 million in profits, about 3.5 times of the investment.</p>
<h2 id="looking-ahead">Looking Ahead</h2>
<p>Looking forward, I will continue optimizing this trading methodology to pursue long-term steady profits. I will also share my trading insights continuously through my blog.</p>
<p>Thank you for reading and I look forward to advancing together on this trading journey!</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About</title>
        <author>
            <name>Winrich</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://imwin.org/about.html"/>
        <id>https://imwin.org/about.html</id>

        <updated>2023-07-25T04:33:06+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    
  <div class="post__toc">
    <h3>fdafadfasdf<br>dfa<br><br></h3>
    <ul>
      
    </ul>
  </div>
  
<pre class="line-numbers  language-html"><code>fadfadsfdsafadsvavdsafadfadsf</code></pre>

  <div  class="gallery-wrapper">
    <div class="gallery" data-columns="3">
      
    </div>
  </div>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <div class="post__toc">
    <h3>fdafadfasdf<br>dfa<br><br></h3>
    <ul>
      
    </ul>
  </div>
  
<pre class="line-numbers  language-html"><code>fadfadsfdsafadsvavdsafadfadsf</code></pre>

  <div  class="gallery-wrapper">
    <div class="gallery" data-columns="3">
      
    </div>
  </div>


  <ul>
    <li>dcfsaf</li><li>adsfdsfas</li><li>fadsfasf</li><li>asdfasdf</li><li>asdfas</li><li><br></li>
  </ul>
<div>html  <html>

</div>

  <p>
    dsfdasfdasfadsf<br>dasfadsfa<br>sdf<br>asdfas<br>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
